# **CV Dawid Kuzbiel**

Junior IT Support/Operations technician

- **f** Kungsbacka
- **0734-08 08 08**
- Dawid.Kuzbiel@gmail.com
- in www.linkedin.com/in/dawidkuzbiel
- www.github.com/madebydawid



I am a Junior IT Support/Operations technician. Specialized in IT Technical Support within Microsoft 365, customization and administration linked to Azure. Solution-oriented with strong analytical skills and a great team player. Certified and updated on the latest industry trends.

## **SKILLS**

**Technical Skills:** • Microsoft 365 Administration • Server Administration (*Windows, Linux*) • Active Directory • Operating Systems (*Windows, Linux, MacOS*) • Networking • Scripting (*Bash, PowerShell*) • Virtualization (*VM-Ware, Hyper-V, Oracle VM VirtualBox*) • Cloud Platforms (*Azure*) • Version Control (*Git, GitHub*) • Troubleshooting • HTML • CSS •

**Soft Skills:** • Effective Communicator • Resourceful • Support-oriented • Fast Learner • Adaptable • High Social Skills

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- SC-900: Security, Compliance & Identity fundamentals (Currently Pursuing)
- AZ-900: Azure Fundamentals (Currently Pursuing)
- MS-900: 365 Fundamentals Cloud
- Cisco Networking Basics
- Cisco Operating Systems Basics
- ITIL 4



# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2019 - 2024

Behavioral Scientist / Aranäsgymnasiet, Kungsbacka

As a behavioral scientist I worked with students and faculty members in the local upper secondary school. My responsibilities included handling student cases, conducting support sessions, conflict resolution, academic guidance, and meetings with students and guardians. Additionally, I contributed to health promotion efforts by developing and delivering lectures, workshops, and guidelines. During these activities, I performed technical troubleshooting tasks such as resolving projector or TV screen issues, screen sharing, changing HDMI cables, and ensuring software compatibility using tools like PowerPoint, Word, video-editing software, and Windows functionality.

IT Tools: Microsoft 365, Windows 10, MacOS, Teams

#### 2018 - 2019

Project Leader/Roofia AB, Kungsbacka

Developed, planned, and coordinated materials and production. Managed customer and supplier contacts. Created drawings, cost estimates, and calculated comprehensive solar panel solutions. I was responsible for providing solutions to our customers, which required personal organization, structure, and flexibility due to the challenges of implementing a new solar panel project.

IT Tools: PvSolar, Outlook, Windows

#### 2018

Counselor/Cityläkarna, Borås

Conducted assessment sessions and ongoing therapy with patients suffering from various mental health disorders including depression, anxiety, panic attacks, grief processing, and stress management. Required empathetic approach, active listening, reliability, interpersonal skills, and sensitivity in disease analysis and selection of tools to assist patients effectively. Managed documentation and confidentiality as part of the role.

IT Tools: Windows, Documentation software

2015 - 2017

Welder and Assembler/Reppu Svets och Montage AB, Trelleborg

2014 - 2015

Welder/Premier Service AB, Borås

2007 - 2014

Welder/Camfill FARR AB, Borås

## **EDUCATION & COURSES**

## April 2024 - August 2024

IT-Support/Operation Technician/Lexicon IT Proffs, Stockholm

- MS-900: Microsoft 365 Fundamentals Cloud Fundamentals of Microsoft 365.
- SC-900: Microsoft 365 Security Fundamentals Security basics for Microsoft 365 & Azure.
- MS-500: Microsoft 365 Security Administrator Advanced security for Microsoft 365 & Azure.
- MD-102: Endpoint Administrator Windows operating system installation and administration.
- **MS-700 Teams Administrator** Deployment, administration and troubleshooting of Teams in a corporate environment.
- Cisco Networking Basic Fundamentals course in Cisco-networking and computer communications.
- Virtualization & Hyper-V Virtualization focused lab environment.
- AZ-800 Server 2022 Server management in hybrid environments on-premises & Azure
- AZ-900 Azure Fundamentals Covers Azure broadly, with an overview of functionalities and services.
- Information Security Data integrity and confidentiality
- PowerShell In several course modules listed above
- ITIL 4 Certification

#### 2015 - 2018

Bachelor Cognitive Neuroscience/University of Skövde, Sweden

Bachelor of Science in Cognitive Neuroscience, emphasizing analytical thinking, problem-solving, and understanding of human behavior and cognition. Proficient in data analysis, research methodologies, and critical thinking, with a strong foundation in scientific inquiry and interdisciplinary approaches. Seeking to leverage cognitive science insights to contribute effectively to IT projects and solutions.

# **ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCES & PROJECTS**

## 2024

## Virtual Lab Environment

I created a virtual lab environment using Oracle VM. Installed Windows Server 2019 with a Domain Controller, configured DHCP, DNS, and Active Directory. Simulated an organization by adding over 1000 users to AD using a PowerShell script. Project can be found on my GitHub page (*Link in info on page 1*).

IT Tools: Oracle VM, Windows Server 2019, Windows 10 Pro, DHCP, DNS, DC, AD, PowerShell

## 2023

## **DNS Spam & Ad Blocker**

I Installed and configured an ad blocker service on my Raspberry Pi, for filtration of unwanted ads on my homenetwork and all connected devices. I also made it my default DHCP server for IPv4 distribution to my homenetwork.

IT Tools: Linux, IPv4, DNS, SSH

I like to challenge myself with the exposure of different IT technologies • Canoeing & Camping • Martial Arts • Golf • Philosophy

# **LANGUAGES**

**English** – Excellent verbal and written communication skills.

**Swedish** – Excellent verbal and written communication skills.

**Polish** – Native language.

## REFERENCES

Good references available upon request.